How many women have I had sex with?
僕は今まで何人の女性とセックスをしてきたのだろうか
Lately, the memories in my head seem to be disappearing little by little.
最近、僕の頭の中の記憶は少しずつ消えていくようだ
Encounters are sad things, and they will surely disappear someday.
出会いとは悲しいもので、いつか必ず消えてなくなってしまう
It's like life.
それはまるで人生のような
So, in order not to lose the life I have lived,
だから僕はこの歩んできた人生を失わないために、
As a record along with the video,
映像と共に記録として、
Yes, so that I can meet you anytime.
そう、 いつでも君に出会えるために
Sister, sister.
お姉さん、お姉さん
Sister, I'm sorry.
お姉さん、すいません
Sister, I didn't drop the key.
お姉さん、鍵落としませんでした、
some time ago.
さっき
Ah, it's mine.
あ、私のです
Oh, your sister was there?
あ、お姉さんあった?
Sorry, I thought you could wear a skirt.
すいません、スカートできたかと思ってました
Mechus, who found me,
見 つけてくれたメチュースとか、
May I?
いいですか?
What's your name? Come to think of it, what's your name?
名前、そういえば何て言うの?
Nana.
ナナ
I haven't been feeling well for a while.
なんか、ずっと元気ないけど
Did something happen?
なんかあったの?
Hmm, actually...
うーん、なんか実はさ...
What, do you mean you're going out to play?
え、遊びに行くってこと?
Who is this child?
この子は誰だ?
Yeah.
うん
Why are you in the same room?
なんで一緒の部屋にいるんだ?
Is that the girl who did it yesterday?
昨日やった子か?
No, in the first place, we probably didn't have sex yesterday.
いや、そもそも昨日セックスはしていないはずだ
No, wait.
いや、待てよ
Is it the child from two days ago?
2日前の子か
No.
ダメだ
I can't remember at all.
全然思い出せない
Who the hell is this kid?
この子は一体誰なんだ?
That's right, let's find out his name and have sex anyway.
そうだ、名前を聞き出して、とりあえずセックスしてみよう
I'm sure you'll remember it that way.
そうすればきっと思い出せるはずだ
What, what did the person you called earlier say?
え、さっき電話してた人に何て言われてるの?
Eh, just Nana.
え、普通にナナ
Nana?
ナナ?
Yeah.
うん
They call me Nana.
ナナって言われてるんだ
Yes, that's right.
そうだよ、そりゃそうだじゃん
Ah, well, why don't we have sex for now?
あ、さ、とりあえずエッチしない?
picture?
え?
Well then, let's have sex.
じゃあ、エッチしようか
Yeah, okay.
うん、いいよ
When was the last time you had sex?
この前、いつしたっけ、エッチ?
Well, I don't know.
えー、分かんない
Don't you remember?
覚えてない?
That's it.
そんなの
Don't you remember?
覚えてない?
Huh, when?
え、いつ?
Huh, wasn't it about a week ago?
え、1週間ぐらい前じゃない?
About a week ago?
1週間ぐらい前?
Why don't you remember?
なんで覚えてないの、逆に?
No, I remember.
いや、覚えてるよ
real?
ほんと?
I remember, I remember.
覚えてる覚えてる
Can I leave it out?
抜かしていい?
Yeah.
うん
Can you feel my boobs?
おっぱい、感じる?
Yeah.
うん
Should I remove this too?
これも抜く?
Chikuri, can you feel it?
ちくり、感じる?
Yeah.
うん
Eh, what's wrong with the red one here?
え、どうしたの、ここの赤いの?
Wow, it's turning red though.
すごい、赤くなってるけど
Hey, the last time we went to a concert together, he said he got bitten by a crab.
え、この前一緒にコン行った時、カニ刺されたって言ったじゃん
Oh, yeah, is that so?
あ、そう、そうだっけ?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうだよね
Yes, I was stabbed at that time.
そうだ、あの時刺されたよね
Yeah.
うん
That's right.
そうだ
Your name is Nana.
君の名前はナナ
I've been remembering it little by little.
少しずつ思い出してきたよ
確
You always wore the same clothes when we met.
か 君は会うときはいつも同じ服だった
But you're always bright and energetic,
でもそんな君はいつも明るく元気で、
I always got energy from you.
僕はいつも君から元気をもらっていたんだ
And you're always in my mouth
そしていつだって君は僕の口に
He did the same thing over and over again.
何 度も同じことをしてくれていたんだ
happiness?
幸せ?
happiness.
幸せ
happy?
ハッピー?
happy.
ハッピー
i love you?
愛してる?
I don't love you.
愛してない
I don't love you at all.
全然愛してない
I still can't remember everything.
まだ全部思い出せない
Just a little more, just a little more.
あと少し、あと少しなんだ
I'll remember it next time.
次こそ思い出そう
It's a feller.
フェラーだ
So, can you give me a blow job?
じゃあフェラーしてくれる?
Yeah, okay.
うん、いいよ
Then I'll take it off.
じゃあ脱ぐね
Shall I put it in then?
じゃあ入れよっか
Yeah.
うん
Make sure to wear a proper rubber band.
ちゃんとゴムつけてね
picture?
え?
Yeah.
うん
That's right.
そうだ
I remembered everything.
全て思い出した
I have to remain in her memory.
僕は彼女の記憶に残らないといけないんだ
My first encounter with her started when I woke her up at an intersection.
彼女との出会いは交差点で起こした回から始まったんだ
Even if my memory is lost, her memory will remain.
僕の記憶が失われても、彼女の記憶は残り続ける
Did something happen?
何かあったの?
Hmm, actually...
うーん、実はさ...
In order to solve her problems, I decided to do it live next time.
彼女の悩みを解決するために、だから次は生でやるって決めていた
I did.
んだ
So, let's decide now.
だから、 だから今決めよう
Our Nijo.
僕たちの二条
I'll change the rubber a bit.
ちょっとゴム変えるね
Hey, is the rubber different from before?
ねえ、さっきとゴム違う?
No.
違うよ
Isn't it different from usual?
なんかいつもと違くない?
copper?
どう?
It feels better than usual.
いつもよりなんか気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
I'll put it in then.
じゃあ入れるね
The rubber is worn out.
ゴムやがれてるじゃん
It was raw.
生だったの
It's not raw.
生だめだよ
I can have a child.
子供できちゃうよ
No.
だめだよ
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
Even if I have a child, I will take responsibility.
子供できても責任取るよ
So let's do it raw.
だから生でしようよ
No.
だめだよ
The truth is, Shin-kun is also sick,
本当はね、シン君も病気のせいで、
Someday I will disappear from my memory, and then I will live and have a child.
いつか記憶の中から私が消えて、それで生でして子供ができるのは
It was scary.
怖 かったの
So even if we have a child, Shin-kun, you'll forget about me and the child.
それでさ、子供ができても、シン君私と子供のこと忘れちゃうのが
It was so scary.
すごい 怖かった
That's why I didn't want to do it live.
だから生でしたくなかったの
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
I won't disappear or disappear.
俺は消えたりいなくなったりしないよ
As long as I exist in Nana's memories, I will always be by her side.
ナナの記憶に俺が存在する限り、俺はずっとそばにいるから
It's true.
本当だよ
Can I put it inside?
中に出していい?
It's not a promise that we'll be together forever,
ずっと一緒にいるって約束じゃなくて、
Let's decide.
決めよう
I'll put it inside.
中に出すよ
Can I take it out?
出していい?
I'll put it out.
出すよ
I'll go.
行くよ
I had a child.
子供ができたの
In this way, I regained Nanata's memory,
こうして僕は、ナナタの記憶を取り戻し、
I was supposed to be happy.
幸せになるはずだった
However, my serious illness did not go away.
だけど僕の重い病気は、消して治りはしなかった
Encounters are sad things, and they will surely disappear someday.
出会いとは悲しいもので、いつか必ず消えてなくなってしまう
Time is equal for all beings.
時間は全ての存在にとって平等だ
But life is not fair.
だけど人生は平等ではない
Some people have long lives;
長く生きる人生を持っている人もいれば、
There are people in life who will die tomorrow.
明日死んでしまう人生の人もいる
Life is not equal, but we all end up in the same place.
人生は平等ではないけれど、最後にたどり着く場所はみんな同じ場
I believe that it is.
所 だと僕は信じている
I believe that there is a world where everyone is equal and peaceful.
そこはみんな平等で、平和な世界だと僕は信じている
I record this unequal life,
そんな平等じゃない人生を僕は記録として、
I want to leave it in whatever form it takes.
どんな形でもいいから残したい
There are people who see that, and you can give them anything, no matter what.
それを見てくれる人がいて、何でもいいから何かを与えることが
If I can do that, I'll be really happy.
でき たら、僕は本当に幸せだ
Lastly, I would like to convey this to everyone.
最後に全ての人へ伝えたい
People are born with a meaning to life,
人 は生きる意味があって生まれ、
There is absolutely no such thing as a useless existence.
決して無駄な存在であるということは絶対にない
As long as you remain in someone's memory, your existence will remain forever.
誰かの記憶に残り続ける限り、自分の存在は永遠に残り続ける
I can't change the present or the past, but
現在や過去は変えられないけれど、
The future can be changed.
未来は変えられるはずだ
So let's live strongly now, for the sake of the future.
だから今を強く生きよう、未来のために
I'll have it then.
じゃあいただきます
What should I do?
どうにしようかな
Well then, this is it.
じゃあ これで
Asa, is there no sex for now?
あさ、とりあえずエッチない?
No?
ダメ?
It's not bad, but it's fine.
ダメじゃないけど、いいよ
Morning, for now...
あさ、とりあえず...
Wait, wait, what should I say?
待って待って、何て言えばいいんだ?
Asa, for now...I'm sorry.
あさ、とりあえず...ごめん
Ah, why don't we have sex for now?
あ、とりあえずエッチしない?
If you laughed, it would have been cut.
笑ったらカットでしたね
Didn't you feel it?
感じなかったっけ?
Don't you feel it?
感じない?
Yeah.
うん
Is that so?
そうだっけ?
No.
ダメだよ
Yes, no.
はい、ダメ
Sideways, sideways.
横に、横に
No good
ダメ
Yes.
だ よ
Because of my illness, someday my memory will no longer be about me.
しんくん思い病気のせいで、いつか記憶から私のことなくなって、
So...
それで...
That's no good.
ダ メだよ
The truth is, I was worried because of my illness.
本当はね、しんくん思い病気のせいで、
Someday I will disappear from your memory and...
いつか記憶の中から私は消えて、それで...
So what?
それで何?